Finding Aid for Penn Central Transportation Company Records 1835-1981
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Ann Arbor Railroad Company, 1896-1964; 67 linear feet
  - Labor Relations Files
    - Numbered Files
      - A522 Six-Hour Day, 1932-1937
        - 2) Train and Engine Service Employees, 1932; 1936-1937 (Box 37)
        - 3) Maintenance of Way, Signalmen, 1932 (Box 37)
        - 4) Maintenance of Equipment, Stores, 1932 (Box 37)
        - 5) Station Forces, Clerks, Agents, Telegraphers, Dispatchers, Police Forces, Dining Car Employees, 1932 (Box 37)
        - 6) Marine Employees, 1932 (Box 37)
        - 7) Bureau of Information Eastern Railways, Circular Letter No. 1424 (Box 37)
      - A524 Seniority: Conductors, Trainmen, Yardmen, Radio Operators, 1932-1952 (Box 38)
      - A525 Yardmasters: General, 1932-1958
        - 1) Yardmasters Performing Duties of Switchmen, 1940 (Box 38)
      - A526 Telegraphers, 1934-1956
        - 1) Sunday and Holiday Rules, 1928-1960 (Box 38)
        - 2) Claims, 1951-1959 (Box 38)
        - 3) Starting Time, 1956 (Box 38)
        - 4) Claim, 1958 (Box 38)
      - A528 Delaware and Hudson Railroad: Pay Rates and Rules, 1932 (Box 38)
      - A531 Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1932; 1952 (Box 38)
      - A532 Enginemen, Conductors and Trainmen, Yardmen, 1939-1951 (Box 38)
      - A535 Independent Shopmen on the Eastern Lines, 1933 (Box 38)
      - A537 Emergency Railroad Transportation Act: Equalization of Work, 1933
        - 6) Company Unions, 1934 (Box 38)
        - 7) Progress Report, 1933 (Box 38)
        - 8) Excessive Overtime, 1933 (Box 38)
        - 9), 1958-1960 (Box 38)
      - A538 Claims: Engineers and Firemen, 1960 (Box 38)
      - A539 Time Claims: Away from Home Terminal Time, 1937-1959 (Box 39)
      - A540 Overtime; Boards of Adjustment, 1939; 1953-1958 (Box 39)
      - A541-1 Special Board of Adjustment, Train and Enginemen, 1953 (Box 39)
      - A542 Train or Car Limit Law, 1934-1951 (Box 39)
      - A544 National Railroad Adjustment Board
        - 4) Determinations of Craft or Class of the National Mediation Board, 1934-1948 (Box 39)
        - 6) Rules, Complaints, Decisions, 1934-1960 (Box 39)
        - 12), 1935-1936 (Box 40)
        - 13), 1934-1942 (Box 40)
        - 14), 1934-1949 (Box 40)
        - 22) Attorney General's Committee on Administrative Procedure, 1940-1941 (Box 40)
      - A545 National Mediation Board, 1934-1958 (Box 40)
      - A548 Maintenance of Way Employees, 1934-1954 (Box 40)
      - A549 Railway Labor Act: Amendments, 1934; 1951-1960 (Box 40)
      - A551 Marine Department
        - 1) Marine Cooks and Stewards Union, 1934-1945 (Box 40)
        - 2) Marine Arbitration Case: Licensed Deck Officers' Schedule Revision (Box 40)
          - 1952-1953 (Box 40)
          - 1948-1957 (Box 41)
          - 1935, 1937; 1960 (Box 42)
        - 3) Marine Engineers, 1936; 1958 (Box 43)
        - 4), 1940 (Box 43)
        - 5) Wage Schedules: Ann Arbor Car Ferries (Box 43)
        - 6) Seafarers' Union: Health and Welfare Plan, Pay and Working Conditions, 1948-1960 (Box 43)
        - 6) Lake Michigan Car Ferries and Independent Car Ferry Workers Union, 1934-1954 (Box 44)
        - 6), 1938-1956 (Box 45)
        - 9) Repairmen, 1955-1959 (Box 45)
      - A552 Pullman Company, 1934-1958 (Box 45)
      - A553 Payrolls: General, 1935-1958 (Box 46)
      - A554 Shop Employees, 1935-1962
        - 1) Oilers (Carmen Helpers) and Shop Crafts, 1936-1937 (Box 46)
        - 2) Shop Crafts, 1936-1959 (Box 46)
        - 3) Shop Crafts, 1937 (Box 46)
        - 4) Shop Crafts, 1937-1944 (Box 46)
        - 6) Shop Crafts, 1939 (Box 46)
        - 7) Shop Crafts, 1951-1956 (Box 46)
        - 9) Shop Crafts, 1938-1958 (Box 46)
      - A559 Joint Trackage Rights, 1935-1960 (Box 46)
      - A560 Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1935-1950 (Box 46)
      - A564 American Radio Telegraphists Association, 1936-1938 (Box 46)
      - A565-1 Yardmen, 1937-1941 (Box 46)
      - A567 Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1936-1960
        - 1), 1941-1944 (Box 47)
      - A569 Dismissal, Suspensions and Discipline, 1937-1961
        - 1), 1936-1952 (Box 47)
        - 2), 1936-1960 (Box 47)
        - 3), 1941-1942 (Box 47)
        - 4), 1959 (Box 47)
      - A572 Telegraphers Organization, 1936-1960 (Box 47)
      - A573 Wabash Special Service Department, 1936-1960 (Box 47)
      - A575 Railroad YMCAs Upkeep and Maintenance, 1937 (Box 47)
      - A576 Use of Self-Propelled Machines, 1937-1959 (Box 47)
      - A577 Wage Increases: General, 1944-1953
        - 1) Maintenance of Way Employees, 1937-1950 (Box 47)
        - 2) Clerks, 1937-1950 (Box 47)
        - 3) Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1937 (Box 47)
        - 3-1) Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1941 (Box 47)
        - 3-2) Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1942-1955 (Box 47)
        - 4) Shop Crafts, 1937-1953 (Box 47)
        - 5) Marine Engineers, 1937 (Box 48)
        - 5-1) Marine Engineers, 1941-1948 (Box 48)
        - 6) Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1937-1948 (Box 48)
        - 6-1) Conductors, Trainmen, Yardmen, Engineers, Firemen, 1941-1943 (Box 48)
        - 6-2) Train and Engine Service Organizations, 1942-1944 (Box 48)
        - 7) Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1937-1950 (Box 48)
        - 7-1) Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1941 (Box 48)
        - 8) Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1937-1940 (Box 48)
        - 8-1_ Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1941 (Box 48)
        - 8-2) Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1942-1950 (Box 48)
        - 9) Supervisory Officers, 1937-1960 (Box 48)
        - 10) Yardmasters, 1937-1953 (Box 48)
        - 11) Unlicensed Marine Department Employees, 1944-1953 (Box 48)
        - 12) Dispatchers, 1939-1949 (Box 48)
        - 13) Non-operating Railway Labor Organizations, 1937-1944 (Box 48)
        - 15) Eastern Carriers Conference Committee, 1941 (Box 49)
        - 16) Linemen (Box 49)
        - 17) Pursers and Radio Operators, 1941-1950 (Box 49)
        - 18) Shore Watchmen, 1942-1957 (Box 49)
        - 19) Mechanical Department Supervisors and Foremen, 1945-1953 (Box 49)
      - A580 Telegraphers, 1936-1959 (Box 49)
      - A581 Mail, Baggage, Express and Freight Handling, 1958-1959 (Box 49)
      - A582 Final Terminal Overtime, 1937-1956 (Box 49)
      - A583-1 Pay Claim, 1955 (Box 49)
      - A584 Electric Lanterns, 1935-1947 (Box 49)
      - A585 Claim, 1937 (Box 49)
      - A586 Hostlers, 1951-1957
        - 1) Employment of Outside Hostler Helpers, 1937-1941 (Box 49)
        - 2) Inside Hostlers and Laborers (Box 49)
        - 3), 1941-1944 (Box 49)
      - A587 Student Employees, 1937-1959 (Box 49)
      - A590 Conferences, 1938-1956 (Box 49)
      - A591-1 Wash Rooms, Lockers, Bunks, Washing Facilities on Yard Engines, 1938-1956 (Box 49)
      - A591-2 Equipment: Furnishing Tools to Employees, 1944-1953 (Box 49)
      - A591-4 Flashlights, 1949 (Box 49)
      - A593-1 Passes, 1941-1963 (Box 49)
      - A594 Attending Investigations, Inquests, or Court, 1938-1961 (Box 49)
      - A597 Seniority: Enginemen, 1939-1957 (Box 49)
      - A597-2 Seniority: Masters, Mates, Pilots, Marine Engineers, 1945-1952 (Box 49)
      - A599 Puller Service, 1938-1952
        - 1), 1940-1943 (Box 49)
        - 2), 1940-1960 (Box 49)
        - 3), 1940-1943 (Box 49)
        - 4), 1940-1941 (Box 49)
        - 5) (Box 49)
      - A601 Individual Claims, 1939-1963
        - 1), 1943-1960 (Box 49)
        - 2), 1939-1949 (Box 49)
        - 3), 1941-1956 (Box 49)
        - 4), 1948-1954 (Box 49)
      - A602 Subordinate Officials and Employees, 1937-1958 (Box 50)
      - A606-2 Trainmen, 1950-1959 (Box 50)
      - A607 Conferences of Executive Officers, 1939-1960 (Box 50)
      - A608 Claim, 1945 (Box 50)
      - A609 Claim, 1939-1943 (Box 50)
      - A610 Claims, 1939-1959 (Box 50)
      - A613 Musicians Union, 1939 (Box 50)
      - A613-2 Lighter Captains Union, 1940-1957 (Box 50)
      - A614 Individual Claims, 1945-1954 (Box 50)
      - A616 Individual Claims: Yardmen, 1943-1960 (Box 50)
      - A617 Clerks, 1940 (Box 50)
      - A620 Railway Employees' Department of American Federation of Labor: Agreement for Handling Jurisdictional Disputes, 1940-1958 (Box 50)
      - A621 Claim, 1957 (Box 50)
      - A627 Shop Crafts, 1940-1941 (Box 50)
      - A629-1 Claim, 1940 (Box 50)
      - A630 Claim, 1958-1959 (Box 50)
      - A631 Assignment of Flagmen on Self-propelled Machines, 1948-1955 (Box 51)
      - A634 Fair Labor Standards Act: Industry Committee, 1940-1945
        - 1) Applications of Fair Labor Standards Act to Radio Operators, 1941-1950 (Box 51)
      - A638 Complaint of O.R.T., 1940-1956 (Box 51)
      - A640 Inspection and Repair of Diesel Locomotives, 1940-1958 (Box 51)
      - A641-1 Request for Change of Apprenticeship Rules, 1940-1953 (Box 51)
      - A641-2 Apprentice Training Program, 1941-1953 (Box 51)
      - A644 Stokers: Claims, Pay Rates, Request for Two Firemen on Engines, 1940-1950 (Box 51)
      - A646 Selective Training and Service Act of 1940 Servicemen's Readjustment Act of, 1944, 1940-1948 (Box 51)
      - A649 Manning of Inter-Railroad Service Trains, 1940-1950 (Box 51)
      - A650 Pool Freight Assignments, 1941 (Box 51)
      - A655 Clerks: Working Less Than Six Days per Week, 1941-1950 (Box 51)
      - A656 Emergency Boards, 1950-1960 (Box 51)
      - A662 Claim by Fireman, 1942-1947 (Box 51)
      - A663 Claims: Yardmen and Enginemen, 1941-1956 (Box 52)
      - A664 Telegrapher, Yard Crews, 1942-1946 (Box 52)
      - A665 Telegraphers: Bulletining Vacancies, 1958 (Box 52)
      - A670 Emergency Acts, Bureaus, Boards and Regulations, etc., created during World War II, 1942-1946
        - 1) Anti-Inflation Act, 1942-1946 (Box 52)
        - 2) National War Labor Board, 1943-1946 (Box 52)
        - 3) Railroad Manpower, 1942-1948 (Box 52)
        - 4) Employment Stabilization (National Association of Manufacturers, 1948) (Box 52)
      - A671 Brief for Supreme Court case: ORT vs. Pennsylvania Railroad Company and Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen, 1944 (Box 52)
      - A671-1 Representation of Repairmen at Elberta, Michigan, Yard, 1953-1955 (Box 52)
      - A675 Employment of Married Women and Working Under Relatives, 1932-1948 (Box 52)
      - A676 Claim of Passenger Crews for Freight Rates, 1943-1948 (Box 52)
      - A678 Act Protecting Reemployment Rights of Persons Serving in Merchant Marine, 1943-1948 (Box 52)
      - A681 Sick Leave Allowances, 1942-1955 (Box 52)
      - A683 Yard Assignments: Starting and Quitting Point, 1943-1958 (Box 52)
      - A687 Enginemen and Trainmen Handling Switches, Flagging and Changing Controls on Diesel Engines, 1944-1955 (Box 52)
      - A689 Claim Engineer, 1944-1951 (Box 52)
      - A690 Learning Road and Terminals, 1944-1953 (Box 52)
      - A691 Claims: Yardmen, 1948-1960 (Box 52)
      - A691 Claims: Yardmen, 1948-1960 (Box 53)
      - A692 Clerks, Yard Clerks, Truckers, 1949-1960 (Box 53)
      - A696 Yard Crews Used Off Assignment, 1944-1945 (Box 53)
      - A697 Payment under Hours of Service Law; Claims of Firemen and Engineers, 1943-1960 (Box 53)
      - A698 Conductors Performing Clerical Work, 1945-1949 (Box 53)
      - A699 Two or More Classes of Service; Engineer's Claims, 1948-1959 (Box 53)
      - A701 Installation and Maintenance of Radio Equipment, 1945-1959 (Box 53)
      - A704 Claims Account: Not Using Firemen on Engines, 1946-1959 (Box 53)
      - A706 Used Outside of Assigned Service or Territory; Firemen's and Engineers' claims, 1945-1953 (Box 53)
      - A708-3 Strike of Unlicensed Marine Employees on Lake Michigan Car Ferries, 1946 (Box 53)
      - A708-5 Strike of Enginemen, Trainmen and Yardmen, 1949-1950 (Box 53)
      - A712 Meal Periods: Telegraphers, 1946 (Box 53)
      - A714 Claims: Train and Engine Service Employees and Engineers, 1947-1956 (Box 53)
      - A715 Claims: Yard Foremen and Engineer; Beginning and End of Day, 1954-1960 (Box 53)
      - A715 Claims: Yardmen, 1954-1960 (Box 54)
      - A716 Workmen's Compensation Act, 1946 (Box 54)
      - A717 Claims: Clerks (use during temporary vacancy), 1952-1956 (Box 54)
      - A718 Engines: Back-up Movements, 1960 (Box 54)
      - A721 Continuous Time: Trainmen and Enginemen, 1948-1960 (Box 54)
      - A722 Yardmen: Switchtenders Piloting Light Engine Movements Within Terminal, 1947-1951 (Box 54)
      - A723 Sleeping Quarters and Hotel Accommodations, 1948-1956 (Box 54)
      - A724 Hostling Service: Engineer Crews, 1947-1957 (Box 54)
      - A725 Designation of Interchange Tracks, 1947-1958 (Box 54)
      - A726 Bulletining Vacancies: Train and Engine Service Employees, 1947-1960 (Box 54)
      - A727 Watching Engines, 1947-1949 (Box 54)
      - A728 Train Service Employees Performing Telegraphers' Service, 1947-1958 (Box 54)
      - A729 Claims: Yardmen, 1947-1952 (Box 54)
      - A730 Claims: Engineers, Conductors, Firemen and Brakemen, 1947-1955 (Box 54)
      - A731 Placing Supplies and Equipment on Cabooses and Engines, 1948-1958 (Box 54)
      - A732 Yardmen Relieving Road Crews Due to Hour of Service Law, 1948 (Box 54)
      - A733 Yardmen: Claims, Abolishing or Creating Yard Assignments, 1956-1960 (Box 54)
      - A735 Payroll Deductions, 1948-1960 (Box 54)
      - A736 Passenger Cars, 1948-1957 (Box 54)
      - A737 Initial Terminal Delay, 1948-1957 (Box 54)
      - A738, 1948-1950 (Box 54)
      - A739-1 Use of Radio by Other Than Operating Employees, 1958 (Box 54)
      - A740 Diesel-electric Locomotive Trains, 1949 (Box 54)
      - A741 Turnaround Service and Claims by Firemen and Engineers, 1949-1960 (Box 54)
      - A742 Conductors and Trainmen Selling Tickets on Trains, 1949-1954 (Box 54)
      - A743 Great Lakes Licensed Officers' Organization, 1950-1951 (Box 54)
      - A746 Inspection and Testing of Locomotives, 1959 (Box 54)
      - A747 Trainmen Handling Gates on Signals, 1952 (Box 54)
      - A748 Claim Engineer and Fireman, 1950 (Box 54)
      - A749 Weight on Drivers of Engines, 1950-1951 (Box 54)
      - A750 Economic Stabilization Agency: Wage and Price Stabilization, Railroad and Airline Wage Board, Office of Price Stabilization Circulars, 1952-1953 (Box 55)
        - 1) Economic Stabilization Agency: Railroad and Airline Wage Board, 1952-1953 (Box 55)
        - A751, 1959 (Box 55)
      - A752 Yard Crews Claiming Additional Time and RASH Conference Cases, 1951-1955 (Box 55)
      - A753 Notifying Organizations When Employees are Killed or Injured, 1951 (Box 56)
      - A757 Yardmen's Claims: 5-6 Day Work Week, Relief Service, Filling Vacancies, 1950-1960 (Box 56)
      - A758 Classification of Employees in Enginehouse Territory, 1952 (Box 56)
      - A761 Establishing or Abolishing Terminals, 1960 (Box 56)
      - A762 Missing Calls, Laying Off and Reporting, 1952-1958 (Box 56)
      - A763 Freight Stations, 1952 (Box 56)
      - A764 Operating Rules: Examination re, 1953-1954 (Box 56)
      - A766 Claims: Yardmen, Yard Foremen, and Helpers, 1954 (Box 56)
      - A767 Contracting or Farming Out Work, 1960 (Box 56)
      - A773 Telegraphers; Deadheading, 1955-1960 (Box 56)
      - A774-1 Right to Work Laws, 1960 (Box 56)
      - A775, 1958-1959 (Box 56)
      - A777 Transportation Furnished by Company, 1956 (Box 56)
      - A778 Claims: Pursers, 1956-1959
        - 1) Holiday Pay for Pursers, 1960 (Box 56)
      - A779 Laying Off and Reporting, 1958 (Box 56)
      - A780 Merging Subsidiary Lines with the Ann Arbor Railroad Company, 1956 (Box 56)
      - A782 Minimum Daily Earnings; Industrial Switching, 1956-1959 (Box 56)
      - A783 Bridges, 1957 (Box 56)
      - A784 Railroads Discontinuing Operations, 1957 (Box 56)
      - A785 Cost of Living, 1957-1959 (Box 56)
      - A788 Eliminating "Extra Gang Foremen" Seniority Roster, Placing Names on Foremen's Roster, 1954-1958 (Box 56)
      - A789 Turntables, 1957 (Box 56)
      - A790 Consolidating Mechanical Department and Stores Department at Owosso, 1958 (Box 56)
      - A795 Hot Boxes, 1959 (Box 56)
      - A796 Linemen, 1957
        - 1) Linemen: Sundays and Holidays, 1960 (Box 56)
      - A797 Labor and Management Improper Practices Act, State of New York, 1959 (Box 56)
      - A798 Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of, 1959 (Box 56)
      - A801 Calling of Crews, 1960 (Box 56)
      - A803 National Labor-Management Foundation, 1960 (Box 56)
      - A804 Reorganization of Railroads, 1960 (Box 56)
    - Other Labor Records
      - Index to Circulars of the Bureau of Information of the Eastern Railways (Box 57)
      - Agreements
        - American Railway Supervisors' Association, 1956 (Box 57)
        - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, and Switchmen's Union of North America, 1941 (Box 57)
        - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1937-1956 (Box 57)
        - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
          - 1950-1957 (Box 57)
          - 1954-1961 (Box 57)
        - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1957 (Box 57)
        - Clerks and Freight Handlers, Schedules for, 1942 (Box 57)
        - Conductors and Trainmen, 1922 (Box 57)
        - Engineers, Motormen, Firemen, and Hostlers, 1922 (Box 57)
        - Foremen's Association of America, and Great Lakes Licensed Officers' Amalgamated Marine Chapter, Number 159, 1949 (Box 57)
        - Great Lakes Licensed Officers' Organization, 1953-1957 (Box 57)
        - Order of Railroad Telegraphers
          - 1955 (Box 58)
          - 1955-1960 (Box 58)
          - Representing Purser-Radio Operators, 1943-1953 (Box 58)
          - Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1954 (Box 58)
          - Train Dispatchers, 1918-1925 (Box 58)
          - Historical Schedules
            - Clerks, 1921-1957 (Box 58)
            - Enginemen, 1922-1956 (Box 58)
            - Telegraphers, 1921-1958 (Box 58)
            - Unlicensed Marine Employees and Repairmen, 1920-1956 (Box 58)
            - Yardmen, 1922-1944 (Box 58)
          - Circular Letters re American Train Dispatchers' Association, 1937-1961; 2 folders (Box 58)
      - Claims Before National Railroad Adjustment Board
        - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1939-1944 (Box 58)
        - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1933-1946; 2 folders (Box 58)
      - Personnel Matters
        - Engineers and Firemen, 1937-1948 (Box 58)
        - Marine Employees, 1948-1957 (Box 59)
        - Miscellaneous Groups of Employees, 1937-1951 (Box 59)
        - Store Department Employees, 1941-1956 (Box 59)
        - Track Supervisors, 1948 (Box 59)
      - Seniority Lists, 1932-1960 (Box 59)
      - Wage Schedules
        - Telegraphers and Telephoners, 1926-1927 (Box 59)
  - Ann Arbor Railroad Company: Subsidiaries
    - Ann Arbor Boat Company
      - Annual Reports, 1952-1953; 1955-1956 (Box 61)
      - Minutes: Extracts, 1943-1958 (Box 61)
    - Manistique and Lake Superior Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports
        - 1925-1950, 1 volumes (Box 61)
        - 1951-1962 (Box 61)
        - 1967-1968, 2 volumes (Box 274)
      - Balance Sheets
        - (volume 3), October 1921-December 1925 (Box 61)
        - (volume 4), 1926-1928 (Box 62)
        - (volume 5), 1929-1931 (Box 62)
        - (volume 6B), 1932-1935 (Box 62)
        - (volume 7B), 1936-1938 (Box 63)
        - (volume 8B), 1939-1941 (Box 63)
        - (volume 9B), 1942-1944 (Box 63)
        - (Pencil Copies), 1948-1951; 1 volumes (Box 64)
        - (Master Copies), November 1953-December 1956; 1 volumes (Box 64)
        - 1956-1959, 1 volumes (Box 64)
        - (Master Copies), 1957-1961; 1 volumes (Box 65)
      - Labor Relations Files
        - Historical Schedules: Trainmen, Enginemen, and Maintenance of Way Employees, 1943-1960 (Box 65)
        - Schedule Revisions: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1944-1950 (Box 65)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors and Stockholders
        - 1909-1919 (Volume 142)
        - 1920-March 28, 1929, 1 volumes (Box 65)
        - May 21, 1929-December 17, 1953, 5 folders (Box 65)
      - Minutes: Extracts, 1942-1963 (Box 65)
      - Report to Michigan Board of Assessors, 1950-1953; 1959 (Box 65)
      - Account book of income and expenses, 1956-1969 (Box 272)
      - Balance sheets, 1958-1963; 2 bundles (Box 272)
      - Miscellaneous financial (Box 272)
      - Report to the Michigan Board of Assessors, 1962-1964 (Box 272)
    - Manistique, Marquette and Northern Railroad Company
      - Minutes, April 1902-March 1906; 1 volumes (Box 66)
      - Report to Michigan Board of Assessors, 1902 (Box 66)
    - Menominee and St. Paul Railway Company
      - Annual Reports, 1952-1957 (Box 66)
      - Minutes: Extracts, 1944-1958 (Box 66)
    - Wabash Radio Corporation
      - Minutes: Extracts, 1944-1949 (Box 66)
- Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad Company, 1912-1965; 5 linear feet
  Records of this railroad are arranged alphabetically by type of material. They consist primarily of reports to the Interstate Commerce Commission, but include as well scattered annual reports, labor relations files, and a report on the possibility of merging with the Ann Arbor Railroad Company.
  - Annual Reports
    - 1912, 1915; 1916 (Box 66)
    - 1961-1963, 1965 (Box 66)
    - 1966, 1968; 1970; 3 volumes (Box 274)
  - Minute book, 1951-1963 (Box 274)
  - Labor Relations Files: Negotiations with Ford Motor Company, 1956-1958; 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Report of Possibility and Effect of Merging Ann Arbor Railroad into Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad, May 18, 1955 (Box 66)
  - Reports to the Interstate Commerce Commission
    - 1928-1936, 8 volumes (Box 66)
    - 1937-1945, 9 volumes; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - 1947-1949, 3 volumes (Box 69)
    - 1951-1960, 10 volumes (Box 69)
    - 1961-1965, 1967; 1969; 1971-1979; 16 items (Box 275)
- New York Central Railroad Company, 1835-1981; 116 linear feet
  The New York Central records have been divided into four series: New York Central Records (prior to November 1, 1869), New York Central and Hudson River Railroad Company, New York Central Railroad Company, and New York Central Railroad Company: Subsidiaries.
  - New York Central Records (prior to November 1, 1869)
    - Annual Reports, 1853-1869; 1 volumes (Box 70)
  - New York Central and Hudson River Railroad Company, November 1869-December 1914
    Records of the New York Central and Hudson River Railroad Company (boxes 60, 70), a predecessor of the New York Central Railroad Company, consist of annual reports for the years 1873-1876, 1878-1879, and 1881-1914, and minutes of the board of directors and executive committee for 1870-1914 and of standing committees for much of that period.
    - Annual Reports
      - 1873-1876, 1878-1879; 1881-1882 (Box 70)
      - 1883-1889 (Box 70)
      - 1890-1899, 1 volumes (Box 70)
      - 1900-1903 (Box 70)
      - 1904-1911 (Box 70)
      - 1912-1914 (Box 70)
    - Minutes of Board of Directors and Executive Committee
      - January 1, 1870-February 4, 1882 (Box 60, Reel 71)
        (microfilm)
      - May 15, 1882-November 17, 1904 (Box 60, Reel 72)
      - December 1, 1904-April 10, 1911 (Box 60, Reel 73)
      - April 17, 1912-December 22, 1914 (Box 60, Reel 74)
      - Index and Record of Board References (New York Central Railroad of 1853), March 20, 1862-July 6, 1868 (Box 60, Reel 74)
    - Minutes of Standing and Executive Committees
      - October 20, 1880-July 24, 1889 (Box 60, Reel 69)
      - September 4, 1889-September 30, 1896 (Box 60, Reel 70)
      - January 23, 1895-November 5, 1903 (Box 60, Reel 71)
  - New York Central Records (following name change from New York Central and Hudson River Railroad Company in December 1914)